[
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a336534643361396461383039366430353636646638383061303631626539383037316238666333336264646161376538346338396564303961313761616138312c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323439363035382c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770111996,
        "question": "Game Handicap: DRX.C (-1.5) vs HANJIN BRION Challengers (+1.5)",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a656434346364653630393235373563313036386235633934333066633966303163633861646462393135306231633935376131643764386636376230393732612c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323439363033302c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770112026,
        "question": "Games Total: O/U 2.5",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a613663623038313131636466353264643863636465653064306166363535353963363233663138343364353465643461323964626439353061313038343433342c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323439353438332c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770109792,
        "question": "Will turnout in the 2025 Honduran general election be between 60% and 65%?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a613663623038313131636466353264643863636465653064306166363535353963363233663138343364353465643461323964626439353061313038343433342c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323439343037302c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770101606,
        "question": "Will turnout in the 2025 Honduran general election be between 60% and 65%?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a366162313235636263363330323766386233316531353433616261663964356430316462313738613332633038363961333231396263616138656338356332642c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323438313936342c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770082154,
        "question": "Will Lady Gaga win 3 Grammys?",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a313161343964663361316165366137633133663238313434356534316266613263663038616439666632336139623063353237383633636231643635303463322c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323438313735362c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770083078,
        "question": "Will Lady Gaga win 2 Grammys?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a366162313235636263363330323766386233316531353433616261663964356430316462313738613332633038363961333231396263616138656338356332642c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323438313031372c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770078034,
        "question": "Will Lady Gaga win 3 Grammys?",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a656538396265366138306539356631306364636161663265336638626562363335613163366330386332623963363762343762613564623633343930376539392c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323437373232312c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770067322,
        "question": "Maryland Eastern Shore Hawks vs. North Carolina Central Eagles (W)",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a393736646637353037343630626131316532353932363937306232663863343162643130326434363934383336633764643764353636396561366634383531322c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323436383132322c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770056186,
        "question": "Games Total: O/U 4.5",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a333736363334376362363232643063303462333534363131393265656163636563383565376462643138656264306563653432666366666662386331366133642c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323430313232382c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769917832,
        "question": "Will Trump talk to Vladimir Putin in January?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a636163376433666438303338626666323532646234386139333463303863633032316662343830366461333861663930313764353865653034653835393733322c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323436363534322c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770052252,
        "question": "U.S. strike on Somalia by February 7?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a353733333038396361653563313763393838646139353063326533396330356230653133376662643764643338313438336233623239623333356237626637632c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323436343436372c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770045716,
        "question": "Will \"Melania\" score at least 10 on the Rotten Tomatoes Tomatometer?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a613161353936373065633935376436373665623732626266636662653535633439336334646662396365613937663466323535646630623038386134656130302c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323434353535382c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770006144,
        "question": "Will Bad Bunny perform at the 2026 Grammy Awards?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a646539636163616233636530626364653565633431373435636562626663653931366466343566316334633263653165346131643636343138353431366436612c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323434343233392c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770002368,
        "question": "Zach LaVine: Assists O/U 2.5",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a613164343761313035363336636266306236643761386164343965343132393235356535613163663561366630623562343538303931666565326637316233332c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323432393036362c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769975710,
        "question": "Mubadala Abu Dhabi Open, Qualification: Hailey Baptiste vs Teodora Kostovic",
        "answer": "P3"
    }
]
